[
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 16?",
      "correctAnswer": "256",
      "options": [
        "256",
        "254",
        "261",
        "258"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 28?",
      "correctAnswer": "784",
      "options": [
        "789",
        "786",
        "784",
        "782"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 57?",
      "correctAnswer": "3249",
      "options": [
        "3254",
        "3249",
        "3247",
        "3251"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 45?",
      "correctAnswer": "2025",
      "options": [
        "2027",
        "2030",
        "2025",
        "2023"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 34?",
      "correctAnswer": "1156",
      "options": [
        "1156",
        "1154",
        "1158",
        "1161"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 52?",
      "correctAnswer": "2704",
      "options": [
        "2704",
        "2709",
        "2706",
        "2702"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 12?",
      "correctAnswer": "144",
      "options": [
        "142",
        "149",
        "146",
        "144"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 58?",
      "correctAnswer": "3364",
      "options": [
        "3366",
        "3369",
        "3364",
        "3362"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 53?",
      "correctAnswer": "2809",
      "options": [
        "2807",
        "2811",
        "2809",
        "2814"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 44?",
      "correctAnswer": "1936",
      "options": [
        "1938",
        "1936",
        "1941",
        "1934"
      ]
    }
]